<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="Temple_of_Karnak">Temple of Karnak, Luxor</string>
    <string name="DTemple_of_Karnak">Within a city of towering obelisks, sanctuaries, and squares,
        Temple of Karnak is part of World Heritage-listed ancient ruins, once probably one of the
        largest religious sites ever built.</string>

    <string name="The_Museum">The Museum of Egyptian Antiquities, Cairo</string>
    <string name="DThe_Museum">Ancient history at its best, The Museum of Egyptian Antiquities boasts
        a collection notable for its standout pieces and, with a total of around 120,000 pieces,
        for its depth. First timers will want to see the Gold Mask of Tutankhamen.</string>

    <string name="Pyramids">Pyramids of Giza, Giza</string>
    <string name="DPyramids">The last of the original Seven Wonders of the World, Pyramids of Giza 
        include a complex of World Heritage-listed ancient monuments, including the Great Pyramid. 
        Dating back to around 2560 BCE, the pyramids were built by thousands of workers under the 
        command of successive pharaohs,</string>

    <string name="Valley_of_kings">Valley of the Kings, Luxor</string>
    <string name="DValley_of_kings">Journey back in time by visiting Valley of the Kings, one of
        the worlds most significant archaeological sites, dating back to the Egyptian New Kingdom.
        The area contains about 63 tombs and chambers, final resting places of pharaohs and nobles.</string>

    <string name="Abu_simble">Abu Simbel Temple Complex, Abu Simbel</string>
    <string name="DAbu_simble">The power of one of the most iconic pharaohs remains evident at Abu
        Simbel Temple Complex, a pair of colossal temples forming part of a World Heritage Site.
        Consisting of the Great Temple and the Small Temple, the complex was built during the reign
        of Ramses II in the 13th century BCE. </string>

    <string name="Medinet_Habu">Medinet Habu, Luxor</string>
    <string name="DMedinet_Habu">Stand in awe of the architecture and artistry of Medinet Habu, the 
        well-preserved mortuary temple of Ramesses III and part of the Theban Necropolis World Heritage Site.</string>
    
    <string name="St_Catherines_Monastery">St. Catherines Monastery, Saint Catherine</string>
    <string name="DSt_Catherines_Monastery">Pay a visit to the World Heritage Site of St. Catherines
        Monastery, a still-functioning Eastern Orthodox monastery that dates back to the 6th century.
        Said to be one of the oldest active Christian monasteries in the world, the ancient walled complex
        lies nestled in the rocky foothills of Mount Sinai.</string>

    <string name="Mosque_of_Muhammad">Mosque of Muhammad Ali, Cairo</string>
    <string name="DMosque_of_Muhammad">Gaze up at the striking array of domes and minarets that make
        Mosque of Muhammad Ali an imposing and ornate place of worship. Constructed on orders of Mohamed
        Ali Pasha between 1830 and 1848, the mosque stands atop a hill and features a 52 m (170 ft) high
        central dome and twin minarets visible from many points around the capital.</string>

    <string name="Philae_Temple">Philae Temple, Aswan</string>
    <string name="DPhilae_Temple">An island temple complex dedicated to the Ancient Egyptian goddess
        Isis, Philae Temple makes up part of a larger set of World Heritage-listed monuments. With hieroglyphs
        and monumental colonnades, the temple displays features from the late Pharaonic era, though alterations
        continued right up to the Byzantine period.</string>

    <string name="Mosque_and_Madrasa_of_Sultan_Hassan">Mosque and Madrasa of Sultan Hassan, Cairo</string>
    <string name="DMosque_and_Madrasa_of_Sultan_Hassan">Reportedly the finest example of early Mamluk
        architecture, Mosque and Madrasa of Sultan Hassan draws tourists not only with its impressive
        exterior and extravagant interior, but also with its rich history. Commissioned in 1356, the
        building is of gargantuan size, unusual egg-shape, with a wooden dome and twin minarets.</string>
    
    <string name="Kharga_Oasis">Kharga Oasis</string>
    <string name="DKharga_Oasis">It is located south Assiut and it has inside the best deep wells that
        have lots of therapeutic benefits including Nasser Wells and Bulaq Wells which are self-flowing
        deep wells, stems at a depth of 1000 meters, and a temperature of 28 ° C, that is surrounded by
        areas of greenery.</string>

    <string name="Bahariya_Oasis">Bahariya Oasis</string>
    <string name="DBahariya_Oasis">Those are some of the most well-known oases in Egypt that are located 
        in the Western Desert. It is a group of Egyptian oases located in the Western Desert 350 km southwest 
        of Alexandria, 370 km from Cairo where it belongs to Giza Governorate.</string>
    
    <string name="Aswan_City">Aswan City</string>
    <string name="DAswan_City">Aswan is a famous tourist city that is located in Upper Egypt and besides
        its majestic ancient &amp; modern attractions that are located on the banks of the Nile River
        it has the most convenient atmosphere that is very relaxing and suitable for the patients who suffer
        from respiratory diseases, kidneys diseases</string>

    <string name="Siwa_Oasis">Siwa Oasis</string>
    <string name="DSiwa_Oasis">Siwa Oasis has the most natural erosion factors that enable it to be
        the most visited natural treatment spot all around Egypt. It contains about natural 230 freshwater
        springs and more than naturally flowing 1000 wells.</string>

    <string name="Ras_Sedr">Ras Sedr</string>
    <string name="DRas_Sedr">It is an awesome tourist town in Sinai Governorate exactly on the Suez
        Gulf. It is a very well-known spot that holds “Ouyoon Moussa” (Moussa’s wells) that dates back
        to the ancient era of Egypt and it witnesses the arrival of Prophet Moses, the Greeks, the Romans,
        and Jesus Christ.</string>
    
    <string name="Dahab">Dahab</string>
    <string name="DDahab">Dahab is located some 85 km (53 miles) north of Sharm el-Sheikh on the Gulf 
        of Aqaba, near the southern tip of Sinai. Once an isolated coastal village, Dahab turned into 
        a hippie hangout in the 1980’s and became something of an “alternative resort”, mixing cheap 
        accommodation with a laid back lifestyle. </string>
    
    <string name="River_Nile_Cruise">River Nile Cruise</string>
    <string name="DRiver_Nile_Cruise">Cruising the Nile is a popular way of visiting upper Egypt. 
        The Nile River has been Egypt’s lifeline since ancient times and there is no better way to 
        trace the passage of Egypt’s history than to follow the course of the Nile.</string>
    
    <string name="Red_Sea_Reef">Red Sea Reef</string>
    <string name="DRed_Sea_Reef">The Red Sea, off the coast of Egypt, is one of the most beautiful
        places in the world to go diving. The waters of the Red Sea are renowned for their spectacular
        visibility and features some of the most exotic seascapes.</string>
    
    <string name="Sharm_el_Sheikh"> Sharm el-Sheikh</string>
    <string name="DSharm_el_Sheikh">Sharm el Sheikh is one of the most popular resort towns in Egypt,
        located at the tip of the Sinai Peninsula. With its warm, deep blue water and great golden beaches,
        Sharm (as it’s affectionately called) is a popular package holiday destination with its own airport.</string>

    <string name="Fjord_Bay">Fjord Bay, Taba</string>
    <string name="DFjord_Bay">Located around 15-kilometers away from the small Egyptian town of Taba,
        near the border with neighboring Eilat in Israel, is a piece of picture-perfect paradise.
        Fjord Bay is the ideal location for diving, whether you have hundreds of hours of diving experience
        under your belt or you fancy giving it a go for the first time.</string>
</resources>